Sarah Clark

123 Main Street, Cepe May, NJ 08204 sarah.clark@youremail.com (123) 456-7890

Business-minded and success-driven secretary with a Business and Technology degree from the Stevens Institute of Technology. Impressive administrative and IT competency, including experience using Microsoft Office and complex customer relationship management systems. Excellent aptitude for customer service both in-person and over the phone and a track record of improving administrative team efficiency. Impeccable ability to remain calm under pressure, work productively in a fast-paced environment and provide efficient solutions to problems.

Key Skills

- Diary and calendar management
- Updating and managing CRM systems
- Office administration and management
- Excellent communication skills via telephone, email, and in-person
- Impeccable computer skills and knowledge of relevant computer systems
- Friendly and professional customer service manner

Professional Experience

Secretary

Gibbons & O 'Neill, Cape May, NJ I January 2017 - February 2021

- Responsible for managing and updating diaries and calendars for senior staff members
- Trained junior members of the team to improve working efficiency by 45%
- Responded to all telephone and email inquiries
- Managed CRM systems
- Scheduled all meetings and interviews
- Work in Excel daily performing data calculation, and creating formulas, charts, and graphs

Secretary

Cape Bookkeeping Tax & Insurance Center, Cape May, NJ j April 2014 - November 2017

- Drafted all meeting agendas and kept notes during meetings
- Responsible for organizing and storing office paperwork
- Issued and created invoices for clients and improve invoicing time by 70%
- Provided administrative support to the company directors
- Responsible for answering all incoming phone calls.

Education

Bachelor Of Science in Business and Technology STEVENS INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY Hoboken, NJ, September 2010 -April 2014

Certifications

 Universal Class Certified General Secretary, 2016, by the New Jersey State Secretary Association